const List<Map<String, String>> elemental = [
  {'question': 'H', 'answer': '수소'},
  {'question': 'He', 'answer': '헬륨'},
  {'question': 'Li', 'answer': '리튬'},
  {'question': 'Be', 'answer': '베릴륨'},
  {'question': 'B', 'answer': '붕소'},
  {'question': 'C', 'answer': '탄소'},
  {'question': 'N', 'answer': '질소'},
  {'question': 'O', 'answer': '산소'},
  {'question': 'F', 'answer': '플루오린'},
  {'question': 'Ne', 'answer': '네온'},
  {'question': 'Na', 'answer': '나트륨'},
  {'question': 'Mg', 'answer': '마그네슘'},
  {'question': 'Al', 'answer': '알류미늄'},
  {'question': 'Si', 'answer': '규소'},
  {'question': 'P', 'answer': '인'},
  {'question': 'S', 'answer': '황'},
  {'question': 'Cl', 'answer': '염소'},
  {'question': 'Ar', 'answer': '아르곤'},
  {'question': 'K', 'answer': '칼륨'},
  {'question': 'Ca', 'answer': '칼슘'},
  {'question': '수소', 'answer': 'H'},
  {'question': '헬륨', 'answer': 'He'},
  {'question': '리튬', 'answer': 'Li'},
  {'question': '베릴륨', 'answer': 'Be'},
  {'question': '붕소', 'answer': 'B'},
  {'question': '탄소', 'answer': 'C'},
  {'question': '질소', 'answer': 'N'},
  {'question': '산소', 'answer': 'O'},
  {'question': '플루오린', 'answer': 'F'},
  {'question': '네온', 'answer': 'Ne'},
  {'question': '나트륨', 'answer': 'Na'},
  {'question': '마그네슘', 'answer': 'Mg'},
  {'question': '알류미늄', 'answer': 'Al'},
  {'question': '규소', 'answer': 'Si'},
  {'question': '인', 'answer': 'P'},
  {'question': '황', 'answer': 'S'},
  {'question': '염소', 'answer': 'Cl'},
  {'question': '아르곤', 'answer': 'Ar'},
  {'question': '칼륨', 'answer': 'K'},
  {'question': '칼슘', 'answer': 'Ca'},
  {'question': '1', 'answer': 'H'},
  {'question': '2', 'answer': 'He'},
  {'question': '3', 'answer': 'Li'},
  {'question': '4', 'answer': 'Be'},
  {'question': '5', 'answer': 'B'},
  {'question': '6', 'answer': 'C'},
  {'question': '7', 'answer': 'N'},
  {'question': '8', 'answer': 'O'},
  {'question': '9', 'answer': 'F'},
  {'question': '10', 'answer': 'Ne'},
  {'question': '11', 'answer': 'Na'},
  {'question': '12', 'answer': 'Mg'},
  {'question': '13', 'answer': 'Al'},
  {'question': '14', 'answer': 'Si'},
  {'question': '15', 'answer': 'P'},
  {'question': '16', 'answer': 'S'},
  {'question': '17', 'answer': 'Cl'},
  {'question': '18', 'answer': 'Ar'},
  {'question': '19', 'answer': 'K'},
  {'question': '20', 'answer': 'Ca'},
];